[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '伝統文化' read in word?",
        "answer": "Традиційна культура"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '娯楽' read in word?",
        "answer": "розваги"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '茶道' read in word?",
        "answer": "Чайна церемонія"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お茶' read in word?",
        "answer": "чай"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '道' read in word?",
        "answer": "шлях"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '書道' read in word?",
        "answer": "Каліграфія"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '書' read in word?",
        "answer": "писати"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '歌舞伎' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кабукі"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '能' read in word?",
        "answer": "Театр Но"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '文楽' read in word?",
        "answer": "Театр Бунраку"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '相撲' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сумо"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '柔道' read in word?",
        "answer": "Дзюдо"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '剣道' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кендо"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '空手' read in word?",
        "answer": "Карате"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '漫才' read in word?",
        "answer": "Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji '落語' read in word?",
        "answer": "Комедійний діалог на сцені・Ракуґо (комічне естрадне оповідання)"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the kanji '囲碁' read in word?",
        "answer": "Ґо"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the kanji '将棋' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сьоги"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the kanji '盆踊り' read in word?",
        "answer": "Танець на фестиваль “Бон”"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the kanji '踊り' read in word?",
        "answer": "Танець"
    }
]